AMANDEEP KAUR

CUSTOMER SUCCESS PROFESSIONAL

Energetic and performance-driven Operations & Client handling Supervisor with 10 years of experience leading teams, improving performance, identifying opportunities, and successfully defusing the toughest clients. Excellent written / verbal communication and interpersonal skills and the ability to respectfully interface with executives from various departments and divisions.

9971280530

Oelhi, India

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/amandeep-kaur-judge

SKILLS

Communication
Positivity
Team Management
Strong work ethic
Operational Support
Client Onboarding
Customer Relationship Building

Escalation Handling
Analytical Skills
Excellent customer service skills
Upselling & Cross-selling products
and services
Identify Customer Needs

Highly organized and detail oriented
Proactive and resourceful Committed to continuous learning
Passionate about customer success

EXPERIENCE

Manager-Customer Support

Easyrewardz Software Solutions Pvt Ltd Dec 2021 - Present

- The company is an enterprise, SME and SMB SaaS, LPaaS provider. Handling a team of
- Customer Support and Campaign executives which involves roster and leave management.
- Customer service portfolio of 90+ brands from retail to BFSI sectors, personally handling three P2 clients.
- Managing and driving the complete Operations for Customer Service and back office activities.
- Planning, streamlining operational processes and quality assurance in day-to-day operations.
- Working on promotional campaigns via various tools (Salesforce, Clevertap etc)
- Setup 3 APAC international contact centers.
- Driving brand specific calling activities.
- Ensure TAT for various activities are met.
- Monthly, quarterly and annual analysis of CS activities and agents.
- Creating checklists and SOPs for brand-specific activities.
- Quality Analysis (QA) of inbound and outbound calls, by regularly auditing the calls.
- Ensure that team maintains AHT and work on CSAT and other related metrics.

Manager- Customer Success & Operations

LegalMD Global Consulting Services Pvt Ltd Apr 2017 - Dec 2021

- Mentoring a team of client support executives to minimize customer churn & focus on retention.
- Working on CRM Salesforce & Zoho to ensure it is always up to date.
- Maintaining a strong working knowledge of clients/Member doctors, medical centres and hospitals and their insurance and legal portfolios with the company.
- Managing client communication through weekly Emails
- SMS deployments for marketing campaigns.
- Establishing coordination between The Backend and Sales Team.
- Closely dealing with our partner Insurance companies and brokers for processing the professional indemnity policy for the Doctors.
- Creating and handling client knowledge base related documents.
- Responsible for maintaining trackers and reporting for Member escalation, team revenue etc.

- Sales (DSR), CSAT, Client Profitabilty Budgeted & Forecast,
- Client Retention, CSE Reports.
- Timely training and inspection of the internal team members.
- Liaising with Vendors and Partners, internal Sales & Accounts team.
- Ensuring Vendor's Invoice and Payment tracking

AM - Client Servicing & Operations

Pramati Healthcare Pvt Ltd Nov 2014 - Mar 2017

- Full-filled client service requirements on confirmed leads received from Sales Team.
- Facilitating post-sales services to existing clients.
- Being SPOC between clients and our organization. Cross-selling and up-selling value-added services to existing clients.
- Responsible for Employee recruitment and onboarding activities. Team Management along with conducting weekly performance review, attendance, refresher training.
- Responsible for updating Client Relationship Module.
- Worked on client's feedback, escalations for their resolutions.
- Controlling employee attrition and retention.
- Strong follow-up and regular interaction for client placement

Business Development and HR Executive

Happy Recruitment Pvt Ltd Nov 2013 - Oct 2014

- Sourcing requirements from HR Department of our clients.
- Finding a suitable candidate profile for required positions online portals.
- · Arranging interviews with concerned HR officials of the companies Closing those openings

BDE & Content Writer

Khoobsurati.com & Growthwell Education Group Aug 2011 - Aug 2013

- Content writing for content marketing and Branding.
- Provided SEO content, Product description and reviews. Written Blogs and Article on several topics for 360 degree coverage.
- Freelance counselor cum BDE with GEG.

EDUCATION

Masters of Business Administration MBA

G.G.S.I.P University Aug 2011 - Aug 2013

Bachelors of Business Administration BBA

G.G.S.I.P University Aug 2007 - Aug 2010

TOOLS

Zoho CRMMS WordAsanaHubspotMS OfficeJIRAPowerpointSales NavigatorZendesksalesforceZapierFreshworks